<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>mwc on Marcos Costales</title><link>https://costales.github.io/tags/mwc/</link><description>Recent content in mwc on Marcos Costales</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 12:23:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://costales.github.io/tags/mwc/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Pensamientos sobre Ubuntu Phone tras la MWC</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/pensamientos-sobre-ubuntu-phone-tras-la/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 12:23:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/pensamientos-sobre-ubuntu-phone-tras-la/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;First they ignore you, then they ridicule you, then they fight you, and then you win&amp;rdquo;.
Siempre me gustó este vídeo de RedHat plasmando la extraordinaria frase de Ghandi. La frase lo simboliza todo. Cuando te propones algo idílico, una quimera, siempre habrá quien no vea más allá de sus narices. Ubuntu nos está señalando la luna, el sueño de todos, un Ubuntu en nuestro bolsillo y mientras, algunos, seguirán mirando su dedo :)</description></item><item><title>MWC - Day 4</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/mwc-day-4/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 15:55:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/mwc-day-4/</guid><description>I told you about tablets, phones, robots&amp;hellip;
&amp;hellip;end of the congress
#history
This last day I want to tell you about everyone who worked so hard these days, inspiring passion every minute and being so nice!! A hug to all of you!</description></item><item><title>MWC - Day 3</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/mwc-day-3/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 23:47:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/mwc-day-3/</guid><description>After the great day of tomorrow (Marius Quabeck uploaded the Mark&amp;rsquo;s keynote here), could be better today? Yes :) Ubuntu won 3 more MWC awards!! WOW!!
Today, I addressed with a gift from Ubuntu France, an orange t-shirt. So bad idea :P It&amp;rsquo;s so similar to the Canonical employees t-shirt in the Ubuntu stand and a lot of people asked me about the phone/tablet. What could I do? Show them my passion about our OS, I think that is the best I could do, because when somebody is passionate about something is so nice to see :)</description></item><item><title>MWC - Day 2</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/mwc-day-2/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2016 10:44:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/mwc-day-2/</guid><description>Today was the big event :)) Mark&amp;rsquo;s keynote.
We wake up at 7:00, then we caught the first tube, but the 2 tube broke :( we had to change the plans direction to the MWC. We returned in the first tube and just in the train Josep sent us a map with the place of the keynote (thanks Josep! you saved us). It wasn&amp;rsquo;t in the MWC! It was near to where we were in that moment!</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu Tablet, best of the MWC 2016!</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/ubuntu-tablet-best-of-mwc-2016/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 20:13:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/ubuntu-tablet-best-of-mwc-2016/</guid><description>Indeed!! Yes :)))
Again!</description></item><item><title>MWC - Day 1</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/mwc-day-1/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2016 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/mwc-day-1/</guid><description>And the MWC started! Thousand of persons around the Congress and a lot of halls and stands.
Finally, we (Marius, Szymon and me) found the Ubuntu stand in the Hall 3. So nice stand, I liked it a lot!! So Ubuntu :))
Ubuntu stand
I saw in there to Josep, a catalan insider how I met in London. So glad to see him again :))
And I saw Javier Pastor too, a Xataka writer.</description></item><item><title>MWC - Day 0</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/mwc-day-0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 09:14:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/mwc-day-0/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m lucky, I&amp;rsquo;ll go to the MWC of Barcelona thanks to an Ubuntu invitation.
This time in the MWC, Meizu and BQ will present an awesome devices and probably Ubuntu will show all of them in its stand.
What I know now is about a convergence tablet from BQ and the most powerfull Ubuntu phone from Meizu.
Both of them will present the devices this monday. That same afternoon, Catalan LoCo team will celebrate an Ubuntu Hour :)</description></item><item><title>MWC Ubuntu Hour in Barcelona!</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/mwc-ubuntu-hour-in-barcelona/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Feb 2016 21:10:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/mwc-ubuntu-hour-in-barcelona/</guid><description>The next week Ubuntu will make history in the MWC!
And the Catalan LoCo team will celebrate it with an Ubuntu Hour |o/
MWC Ubuntu Hour in Barcelona
I&amp;rsquo;ll see you there :))
Info | Location
Poster CC by cfhowlett-a.</description></item></channel></rss>