<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Marcos Costales</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Marcos Costales</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 10:29:27 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://costales.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Clipboard content to file. New app</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/clipboard-to-file/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Oct 2022 10:29:27 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/clipboard-to-file/</guid><description>A simple, easy, fast and useful way to paste your clipboard content (text or image) into a file!
Previously, you had to open editor, paste your clipboard, save file, close editor. Now, right click and choose the menu &amp;ldquo;Clipboard to file&amp;rdquo;!
HOW DOES IT WORK? TEXT Copy a text into your clipboard.
Go to your file browser and do a right click:
Into empty area / &amp;ldquo;Clipboard to file&amp;rdquo; menu: Will create the file clipboard-X.</description></item><item><title>Install k3s cluster into Alpine Linux</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/k3s-alpine-linux/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 10:40:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/k3s-alpine-linux/</guid><description>I'll use Alpine Linux as it is a so light distribution.
My setup is:
192.168.1.100 master 192.168.1.101 node1 192.168.1.102 node2 Into master, let's install requirements, install the master node and get the token:
apk add curl curl -sfL https://get.k3s.io | sh - cat /var/lib/rancher/k3s/server/node-token Into each one of the nodes:
apk add curl k3s_token=&amp;quot;&amp;lt;your_master_token_here&amp;gt;&amp;quot; curl -sfL https://get.k3s.io | K3S_URL=https://master:6443 K3S_TOKEN=${k3s_token} sh - Into the master again, check we see the nodes and config them as workers and disable the master node to run pods:</description></item><item><title>El mejor truco de GMail para filtrar emails</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/gmail-tip-antispam/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 17:03:02 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/gmail-tip-antispam/</guid><description>Tras años usando GMail descrubo el mejor de los trucos: Añadir +texto a tu email, tal que:
tu.email+temporal@gmail.com tu.email+compras@gmail.com Sólo queda filtrar esos emails en GMail como te plazca ;)</description></item><item><title>Install AWX 9 on CentOS 8</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/awx-9-install/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 20:45:48 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/awx-9-install/</guid><description>How to install an older UI AWX on CentOS 8
Needs:
yum -y install epel-release yum -y install ansible git python3-pip yum -y install yum-utils device-mapper-persistent-data lvm2 Docker:
yum-config-manager --add-repo https://download.docker.com/linux/centos/docker-ce.repo yum -y install docker-ce --allowerasing systemctl start docker pip3 install docker pip3 install docker-compose systemctl restart docker systemctl enable docker Check Docker:
docker run hello-world AWX:
git clone -b &amp;quot;9.1.1&amp;quot; https://github.com/ansible/awx.git cd awx/installer/ Change into the inventory file:
localhost ansible_connection=local ansible_python_interpreter=&amp;quot;/usr/bin/env python3&amp;quot; postgres_data_dir=/var/lib/pgdocker awx_official=true project_data_dir=/var/lib/awx/projects awx_alternate_dns_servers=&amp;quot;8.</description></item><item><title>How to upgrade Telegram if you installed it from the package telegram-desktop</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/upgrade-telegram-from-package-telegram-desktop/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 10:10:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/upgrade-telegram-from-package-telegram-desktop/</guid><description>If you installed Telegram in Ubuntu with the package telegram-desktop you'll see that it doesn't update.
You can force it from the official program for desktop. Just run:
cd /tmp wget -O telegram.tar.xz https://telegram.org/dl/desktop/linux tar xf telegram.tar.xz sudo mv Telegram/Telegram /usr/bin/telegram-desktop Now, you only need to restart Telegram ;)</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu y otras hierbas S05E02: Apple M1 y Linux ante ARM. Edge llega a Linux</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/podcast-ubuntu-y-otras-hierbas-s05e02/</link><pubDate>Mon, 28 Dec 2020 20:13:34 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/podcast-ubuntu-y-otras-hierbas-s05e02/</guid><description>¿Será buena para Linux una más que factible migración de x86 a ARM? ¿Significará la muerte de Linux? Creemos que se avecinan tiempos oscuros&amp;hellip;
Y el navegador Edge llega a Linux.
Escúchanos en:
Ivoox Telegram Youtube Y en tu cliente de podcast habitual con el RSS</description></item><item><title>Unav 3 is here!</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/new-unav3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 23:10:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/new-unav3/</guid><description>The new uNav 3 is here!
A simple, easy &amp;amp; beautiful GPS Navigator for Ubuntu Touch!
100% Libre. Doesn't track you, it respects you. Powered by Openstreemap. Online &amp;amp; offline (powered by OSM Scout Server) GPS Navigation. Enjoy it in your UBPorts device!</description></item><item><title>Review Slimbook Pro X</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/review-slimbook-pro-x/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2020 17:39:12 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/review-slimbook-pro-x/</guid><description>Visité Valencia este mes de Julio y aproveché a visitar las oficinas de Slimbook, el manufacturador español especializado en dispositivos con Linux preinstalado. Allí realicé durante un par de horas una review a su modelo Pro X con CPU Ryzen de AMD.
Construcción y diseño Yo uso un Dell Latitude E5470 y al coger el Pro X lo primero que llama la atención es su ligereza (1,1 Kg). No hay muchos portátiles en el mercado que puedan presumir de pesar 1,1 Kg, tal como analicé en otro post.</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu 20.04: Sustituir Nautilus por Nemo</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/ubuntu2004-replace-nautilus-nemo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 10:18:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/ubuntu2004-replace-nautilus-nemo/</guid><description>En Ubuntu 20.04 se incluyó la última versión de Nautilus y la gestión de los ficheros en el escritorio se realiza a través de una extensión de GNOME. Si bien emula correctamente que podamos gestionar ficheros en el escritorio, tiene algunas carencias importantes como no poder arrastrar desde Nautilus al escritorio, atajos de teclado&amp;hellip;
En este vídeo te muestro todos los pasos para sustituir Nautilus por Nemo y conseguir un escritorio totalmente funcional:</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu y otras hierbas S04E08: Ubuntu 20.04 y móviles abiertos</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/podcast-ubuntu-y-otras-hierbas-s04e08/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2020 10:41:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/podcast-ubuntu-y-otras-hierbas-s04e08/</guid><description>Os contamos nuestra impresión con Ubuntu 20.04, en nuestra opinión, la mejor versión de Ubuntu hasta la fecha.
Además analizamos qué alternativas hay para usar móviles abiertos.
Escúchanos en:
Ivoox Telegram Youtube Y en tu cliente de podcast habitual con el RSS</description></item></channel></rss>