<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>apps on Marcos Costales</title><link>https://costales.github.io/tags/apps/</link><description>Recent content in apps on Marcos Costales</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 10:10:21 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://costales.github.io/tags/apps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to updade Telegram if you installed it from the package telegram-desktop</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/upgrade-telegram-from-package-telegram-desktop/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Apr 2021 10:10:21 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/upgrade-telegram-from-package-telegram-desktop/</guid><description>If you installed Telegram in Ubuntu with the package telegram-desktop you'll see that it doesn't update.
You can force it from the official program for desktop. Just run:
cd /tmp wget -O telegram.tar.xz https://telegram.org/dl/desktop/linux tar xf telegram.tar.xz sudo mv Telegram/Telegram /usr/bin/telegram-desktop rm -rf /tmp/Telegram/ /tmp/telegram.tar.xz Now, you only need to restart Telegram ;)</description></item><item><title>Unav 3 is here!</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/new-unav3/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 23:10:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/new-unav3/</guid><description>The new uNav 3 is here!
A simple, easy &amp;amp; beautiful GPS Navigator for Ubuntu Touch!
100% Libre. Doesn't track you, it respects you. Powered by Openstreemap. Online &amp;amp; offline (powered by OSM Scout Server) GPS Navigation. Enjoy it in your UBPorts device!</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu 20.04: Sustituir Nautilus por Nemo</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/ubuntu2004-replace-nautilus-nemo/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Jul 2020 10:18:18 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/ubuntu2004-replace-nautilus-nemo/</guid><description>En Ubuntu 20.04 se incluyó la última versión de Nautilus y la gestión de los ficheros en el escritorio se realiza a través de una extensión de GNOME. Si bien emula correctamente que podamos gestionar ficheros en el escritorio, tiene algunas carencias importantes como no poder arrastrar desde Nautilus al escritorio, atajos de teclado&amp;hellip;
En este vídeo te muestro todos los pasos para sustituir Nautilus por Nemo y conseguir un escritorio totalmente funcional:</description></item><item><title>Yaru &amp; Folder Color in Ubuntu 20.04</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/yaru-and-folder-color-ubuntu-20.04/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 19:45:19 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/yaru-and-folder-color-ubuntu-20.04/</guid><description>The new Yaru in Ubuntu 20.04 is awesome! I love it!
But there isn't an icon theme working fine with Folder Color &amp;amp; Yaru&amp;hellip; until now. Just in time!
Thanks to Jan Schröder with the Yaru-Colors project you can enjoy it now!
How to install it In Ubuntu 20.04 run these commands from a Terminal (from code is available here):
sudo apt install folder-color sudo add-apt-repository ppa:costales/yaru-colors-folder-color sudo apt install yaru-colors-folder-color nautilus -q Thanks All credits are going to Jan Schröder.</description></item><item><title>Install Netflix on Kodi</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/install-netflix-kodi-osmc/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Feb 2020 15:57:39 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/install-netflix-kodi-osmc/</guid><description>I installed Kodi into Raspbian, from the official repository. But here, the Netflix plugin didn't work.
You need to do these steps:
Install the current OSMC release [Now it's OSMC_TGT_rbp2_20191118.img]. sudo apt-get update sudo apt-get upgrade sudo apt-get install python-pip python-crypto build-essential -y sudo apt-get install python-all-dev python-setuptools python-wheel -y sudo apt-get install python-crypto-dbg python-crypto-doc python-pip-whl -y pip install pycryptodomex sudo ln -s /usr/lib/python2.7/dist-packages/Crypto /usr/lib/python2.7/dist-packages/Cryptodome Connect to your OSMC by SSH (Username and password is osmc) Download with wget &amp;lt;URL&amp;gt; the last release from here.</description></item><item><title>uNav 0.75: A libre GPS navigator for your libre pocket device!</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/unav-075-libre-gps-for-your-libre/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Mar 2018 21:02:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/unav-075-libre-gps-for-your-libre/</guid><description>A new release for your Ubuntu Phone powered by UBports!
Why? Because we have a dream \o/
uNav 0.75
Changelog:
Migrated to Openrouteservice. Car | Walk | Bicycle routes. New default map by default powered by Carto. Fixed unit in review the route steps. Install/update it from the Open Store.</description></item><item><title>Píldora snap: Crea una aplicación snap en 5 minutos</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/pildora-snap-crea-una-aplicacion-snap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 19:17:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/pildora-snap-crea-una-aplicacion-snap/</guid><description>En sólo 5 minutos vas a empaquetar tu primera aplicación snap. ¡Más fácil, imposible!
¿Aceptas el reto? ;) ¡Adelante!
vídeo tutorial
Basado en la conferencia de Alan Pope y Martin Wimpress de la 2ª Ubucon Europea:
snap! snap! snap!</description></item><item><title>Folder Color now has emblem file support</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/folder-color-now-has-emblem-file-support/</link><pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2017 11:18:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/folder-color-now-has-emblem-file-support/</guid><description>New release 0.0.85 of folder color! Now you can select a file and set an emblem! Enjoy it! :)
File emblem
How to install?</description></item><item><title>New Folder Color release!</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/new-folder-color-release/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2017 18:40:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/new-folder-color-release/</guid><description>This new version will work with more themes and colors by default!
An easy way make what you’re looking for easier to spot
Any theme with folders like &amp;ldquo;folder-blue&amp;rdquo; will work, even in SVG or PNG, for example: Paper, La Capitaine, etc.
Folder Color in action!
Enjoy it from the PPA of Ubuntu 16.04+!</description></item><item><title>uNav powered by Mapzen! Raising from the darkness thanks to UBPorts!</title><link>https://costales.github.io/posts/unav-powered-by-mapzen-raising-from/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 18:49:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://costales.github.io/posts/unav-powered-by-mapzen-raising-from/</guid><description>Mapzen is moving to a paid API after June 1. This was a big issue to uNav, the map viewer and GPS navigator for Ubuntu Phone.
I had to migrate to the free OSRM router then, but its test server is down several times (it's not a production server) and it has only car navigation mode.
Never fall down! Don't back now!
But, the UBPorts community is surprising me every time!</description></item></channel></rss>